<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 
  ~ Copyright (C) 2015 The Android Open Source Project
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
   -->

<resources xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="description_age_num" msgid="2310840604629413136">"Recommended for ages <xliff:g id="DESCRIPTION_AGE_NUM_ID">%d</xliff:g> and over."</string>
    <string name="description_ar_tv_atp" msgid="275280778758600669">"Suitable for all audiences. Programmes may contain mild violence, language and mature situations."</string>
    <string name="description_ar_tv_sam_13" msgid="395458137803720902">"Suitable for ages 13 and above. Programmes may contain mild to moderate language and mild violence and sexual references."</string>
    <string name="description_ar_tv_sam_16" msgid="5461932730891880296">"Suitable for ages 16 and above. Programmes may contain more intensive violence and coarse language, partial nudity and moderate sexual references."</string>
    <string name="description_ar_tv_sam_18" msgid="967289005476938628">"Suitable for mature audiences only. Programmes contain strong violence, coarse language and explicit sexual references."</string>
    <string name="description_ar_tv_d" msgid="5687319465704756897">"Drugs"</string>
    <string name="description_ar_tv_s" msgid="3649269859977270733">"Sex"</string>
    <string name="description_ar_tv_v" msgid="4115089510428057167">"Violence"</string>
    <string name="description_au_tv_p" msgid="8443265431119407386">"Material classified P is intended for pre-school children."</string>
    <string name="description_au_tv_c" msgid="8211009928919927197">"Material classified C is intended for children (other than pre-school children) who are younger than 14 years of age."</string>
    <string name="description_au_tv_g" msgid="3648769415275928051">"Material classified G is not necessarily intended for children but it must be very mild in impact and must not contain any matter likely to be unsuitable for children to watch without supervision."</string>
    <string name="description_au_tv_pg" msgid="2474110069879436425">"Material classified PG may contain adult themes or concepts but must be mild in impact and remain suitable for children to watch with supervision."</string>
    <string name="description_au_tv_m" msgid="3758823660530867895">"Material classified M is for mature audiences. It is recommended for viewing only by persons aged 15 years or above."</string>
    <string name="description_au_tv_ma" msgid="1560774867226204453">"Material classified MA is suitable for viewing only by persons aged 15 years or over because of the intensity and/or frequency of violence, sexual depictions, or coarse language, adult themes or drug use. The impact may be strong."</string>
    <string name="description_au_tv_av" msgid="9052849694835114072">"Material classified AV is suitable for viewing only by persons aged 15 years or over. It is unsuitable for MA classification because of the intensity and/or frequency of violence, or because violence is central to the theme. In other respects, the requirements of the classification are identical to the MA classification."</string>
    <string name="description_au_tv_r" msgid="5658589437756696378">"Material classified R is legally restricted to adults. Some material classified R may be offensive to sections of the adult community."</string>
    <string name="description_br_tv_l" msgid="3659480129004604299">"General audiences"</string>
    <string name="description_br_tv_num" msgid="8592393496388213855">"Not recommended for ages under <xliff:g id="DESCRIPTION_BR_TV_NUM_ID">%d</xliff:g>."</string>
    <string name="description_br_tv_d" msgid="531580256923909164">"Drugs"</string>
    <string name="description_br_tv_s" msgid="6296128386089692428">"Sex"</string>
    <string name="description_br_tv_v" msgid="4791910148551562553">"Violence"</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_en_exempt" msgid="4594700374681841325">"Exempt programming includes: news, sports, documentaries and other information programming; chat shows, music videos and variety programming."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_en_c" msgid="4239130347733600747">"This programming is intended for younger children under the age of 8 years old."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_en_c8" msgid="157653961756834847">"This programming is intended for youngsters aged 8 years and above. It is suggested that a parent/guardian co-view programming assigned with this classification with children under the age of 8."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_en_g" msgid="9011387267323394838">"This programming is intended for all age groups and therefore appropriate viewing for the entire family."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_en_pg" msgid="1281647966041358531">"This programming, while intended for a general audience, may not be suitable for younger children (under the age of 8). Parents/guardians should be aware that there might be content which some may consider inappropriate for unsupervised viewing by children in the 8-13 age range."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_en_14" msgid="5215879895927351742">"Programming with this classification contains themes or content which might not be suitable for viewers under the age of 14. Parents are strongly advised to exercise caution in permitting viewing by pre-teens and early teens without parent/guardian supervision, as programming with this classification could deal with mature and societal issues in a realistic fashion."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_en_18" msgid="728062003854446182">"This programming is intended for viewers 18 years and older."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_fr_e" msgid="6181168031949930593">"Programmes exempt from classification."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_fr_g" msgid="812712328730700550">"The programme is appropriate for viewing by persons of all ages. A programme with a G rating might offend the sensibilities of children under 8 years of age."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_fr_8" msgid="4710290620628915788">"The programme is suitable for the general public but could contain mild or occasional violence that may disturb young children. Viewing with adult supervision is therefore recommended for young children (age 8 and under)."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_fr_13" msgid="3733179399640639129">"The programme is appropriate for viewing by persons 13 years of age or older. Children under 13 may be admitted only if accompanied by an adult."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_fr_16" msgid="1724956882971714521">"The programme is appropriate for viewing by persons 16 years of age or older. Programmes with this rating present troubling themes, situations or behaviours, and adopt a more direct point of view about things."</string>
    <string name="description_ca_tv_fr_18" msgid="7351531806464525403">"The programme is appropriate for viewing by persons 18 years of age or older. Programmes reserved for adults most often deal primarily with the representation of explicit sexual encounters. They may also be extremely violent, showing scenes of hyperrealistic cruelty, torture and horror."</string>
    <string name="description_es_dvb_all" msgid="7613329223897343137">"Recommended for all ages."</string>
    <string name="description_es_dvb_c" msgid="980267721855879361">"Recommended for children."</string>
    <string name="description_es_dvb_x" msgid="6397110507731134043">"Recommended for adults."</string>
    <string name="description_kr_tv_all" msgid="2880536060037059992">"Programmes do not contain material that is inappropriate for any age, and thus are suitable for everyone."</string>
    <string name="description_kr_tv_7" msgid="6294578566249258989">"Programmes may contain material inappropriate for children under 7, and therefore parental discretion is advised."</string>
    <string name="description_kr_tv_12" msgid="505880672388477268">"Programmes may contain material inappropriate for children under 12, and therefore parental discretion is advised."</string>
    <string name="description_kr_tv_15" msgid="1424825062188417293">"Programmes may contain material inappropriate for audiences under the age of 15, and therefore parental discretion is advised."</string>
    <string name="description_kr_tv_19" msgid="8141648682052815394">"Programmes may contain material inappropriate for audiences under the age of 19, and thus are not suitable for youngsters under 19."</string>
    <string name="description_sg_tv_g" msgid="9207245510001823663">"Suitable for all ages."</string>
    <string name="description_sg_tv_pg" msgid="8807413147853484668">"Suitable for all, but parents should guide their children."</string>
    <string name="description_sg_tv_pg13" msgid="1187187083836621720">"Suitable for persons aged 13 and above but parental guidance is advised for children under 13."</string>
    <string name="description_sg_tv_nc16" msgid="4655362789601793713">"Suitable for persons aged 16 and above."</string>
    <string name="description_sg_tv_m18" msgid="4495688622482686386">"Suitable for persons aged 18 and above."</string>
    <string name="description_sg_tv_r21" msgid="8469412927671691778">"Suitable for adults aged 21 and above."</string>
    <string name="description_th_tv_p" msgid="573604443870633316">"Suitable for children aged 3 to 6."</string>
    <string name="description_th_tv_c" msgid="380126567363659012">"Suitable for children aged 6 to 12."</string>
    <string name="description_th_tv_g" msgid="8696507527665670160">"Suitable for general audiences."</string>
    <string name="description_th_tv_pg13" msgid="1695934461809229216">"Suitable for people aged 13 and above."</string>
    <string name="description_th_tv_pg18" msgid="597070833139949945">"Suitable for people aged 18 and above. And parental guidance for children under 18."</string>
    <string name="description_th_tv_x" msgid="8921473820857112565">"Suitable for adult"</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_d" msgid="7417126048971563355">"Suggestive dialogue"</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_l" msgid="2276830531676175553">"Coarse language"</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_s" msgid="4966533437570326272">"Sexual content"</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_v" msgid="4340768360627689297">"Violence"</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_fv" msgid="5087038597184709325">"Fantasy violence"</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_y" msgid="7153666670476947891">"This programme is designed to be appropriate for all children."</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_y7" msgid="4388896445294252013">"This programme is designed for children aged 7 and above."</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_g" msgid="5919925009580010961">"Most parents would find this programme suitable for all ages."</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_pg" msgid="7696801642081644497">"This programme contains material that parents may find unsuitable for younger children. Many parents may want to watch it with their younger children."</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_14" msgid="1945274614246329605">"This programme contains some material that many parents would find unsuitable for children under 14 years of age."</string>
    <string name="description_us_tv_ma" msgid="7118695706408907620">"This programme is specifically designed to be viewed by adults and therefore may be unsuitable for children under 17 years of age."</string>
    <string name="description_us_mv_g" msgid="299794744638684056">"General audiences. Nothing that would offend parents for viewing by children."</string>
    <string name="description_us_mv_pg" msgid="81027516479177975">"Parental guidance suggested. May contain some material that parents might not like for their young children."</string>
    <string name="description_us_mv_pg13" msgid="2094119267970306011">"Parents strongly cautioned. Some material may be inappropriate for children under 13 years of age."</string>
    <string name="description_us_mv_r" msgid="2248384382323431666">"Restricted. Contains some adult material. Parents are urged to learn more about the film before taking their young children."</string>
    <string name="description_us_mv_nc17" msgid="8734654245083149008">"No one under 17 years of age admitted. Clearly adult. Children are not admitted."</string>
    <string name="description_us_mv_x" msgid="2203823258178769659">"Suitable for adult"</string>
    <string name="description_sa_tv_10" msgid="7534715057755212480">"Children under 10 are prohibited from watching this programme/film."</string>
    <string name="description_sa_tv_none" msgid="2839067796739398528">"Suitable for all ages."</string>
    <string name="description_sa_tv_pg10" msgid="5232468306982287272">"Children under 10 may watch this programme/film, but must be accompanied by an adult."</string>
    <string name="description_sa_tv_pg13" msgid="2826427571649837624">"Children under 13 may watch this programme/film, but must be accompanied by an adult."</string>
    <string name="description_sa_tv_13" msgid="6849007243977700328">"Children under 13 are prohibited from watching this programme/film."</string>
    <string name="description_sa_tv_16" msgid="6934567274078402600">"Children under 16 are prohibited from watching this programme/film."</string>
    <string name="description_sa_tv_18" msgid="6814431681831259975">"Children under 18 are prohibited from watching this programme/film."</string>
    <string name="description_sa_tv_r18" msgid="8966466636870535072">"this is reserved for films of an extreme sexual nature (pornography)."</string>
    <string name="rating_schedule_off" msgid="90379047922234847">"Off"</string>
    <string name="rating_schedule_block" msgid="8052768659911065234">"Block"</string>
    <string name="rating_years" msgid="2286124473198629391">"Years"</string>
    <string name="option_ratings_age" msgid="4730040709343309680">"Age ratings"</string>
    <string name="option_ratings_content" msgid="2743117466268053677">"Content ratings"</string>
    <string name="rating_not_defined" msgid="3930030730202531332">"Not defined"</string>
</resources>
